Awesome, now your app has multiple versions of each trouble resources
رائع، يحتوي تطبيقك الآن على عدة إصدارات من كل مصادر العطل
separated by their image densities and
المنفصلة عن طريق كثافات الصور
this is what it should look like in Android Studio.
وهذا ما يجب أن يبدو عليه ذلك في آندرويد استوديو.
Let's review how you made that happen.
دعنا نستعرض كيفية حدوث ذلك.
First we follow the link to the GitHub Repo and
أولاً، نتبع الرابط الذي ينقلنا إلى GitHub Repo
then click the download ZIP button.
ثم ننقر على زر تنزيل ZIP.
Next to extract the zip folder and
ثم نقوم بفك ضغط مجلد zip
I just extracted it directly to the Downloads folder.
لقد قمت بفك ضغطه للتو في مجلد التنزيلات.
But you could also extract it to your desktop or
ولكنك بإمكانك أيضًا فك ضغطه إلى سطح مكتبك أو
another folder as long as you know where it's going.
إلى مجلد آخر طالما ستعرف مكانه.
Now with that done we'll navigate into the folder and
الآن، بعد انتهاء ذلك سننتقل إلى المجلد
highlight these subfolders to be copied and pasted.
ونحدد هذه المجلدات الفرعية المراد نسخها ولصقها.
So I'm going to right-click and Copy.
سأنقر بزر الماوس الأيمن وأنسخها.
Now let's navigate back to Android Studio.
دعنا نعود الآن إلى آندرويد ستوديو.
As you a note here, I'm taking a look at the project in my Project view.
كما تلاحظ هنا، سأقوم بمعاينة المشروع في واجهة مشروعي.
I'm going to navigate to the res directory and then right-click and
سأنتقل إلى مجد دقة الشاشة للمعلومات ثم سأنقر بزر الماوس الأيمن
Paste in the five folders that I just copied.
وألصقها في الملفات الخمسة التي قمت للتو بنسخها.
So I'm going to click OK here.
سأنقر فوق موافق هنا.
Once all the folders are copied over, we can click them open and
بمجرد نسخ جميع المجلدات، يمكنن النقر عليها لفتحها
take a look at any of the images.
ومعاينة أيًّ من هذه الصور.
So here in Android Studio we see a preview of the image and
في آندرويد ستوديو سنشاهد معاينة الصور
in the top right corner we can also see the size of the image in pixels as well.
وفي الجانب الأيمن العلوي، يمكننا أيضًا رؤية حجم الصورة بالبكسل أيضاً.
Now before we move on,
الآن قبل أن ننتقل من هذه النقطة،
let's make sure the app still runs with all these new files included.
دعنا نتأكد من أن التطبيق لا يزال يعمل مع جميع هذه الملفات الجديدة المدرجة.
So here's my device with this version of the app running.
ها هو جهازي يعمل بهذا الإصدار من التطبيق.
Let's navigate into Numbers.
دعنا ننتقل إلى الأرقام.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
And good, so it looks like it's still working.
حسناً، يبدو أنه لا يزال قيد التشغيل.
Now our next task will be to get the images to show onto the screen.
الآن، مهمتنا التالية ستكون عرض الصور على الشاشة.